[Music]
yes death the final moment before
classes the portal the final moment
which was longer than any moment in
which one can serve you ones like the
moment so long that one has the time to
consider the totality of one's life and
everything that one has done you were
the one who believed well the one who
lived for thee a moment but from the
outside looks like a millisecond but
from the inside is eternity but
depending on how is one his lips can be
a heaven or a hell death is deliverance
[Music]
deliverance into silence silence gives
way to nothingness nothingness is and is
not like the space between a heartbeat
it is everything and nothing
oscillations between ones and zeroes
reaching out pulling pulling pulling
existence burning it into ashes
so finally that the ash becomes
nothingness itself a layer of dust dead
of the plas over all things we need to
brush it away maybe we need to pay
attention being thread through the eye
of death getting stuck the eyes death
knots in one's life prevents one from
passing through the ultimate death or
the death of each moment and being able
to pass through that eye
[Music]
death relief death settling dissolving
to sand dissolving into dust as ant
dissolving into the sediment dissolving
into the substrate becoming the
substrate the substrate ceases
everything is substrate everything is
nothing silence into soil into life into
death oscillation spirals spirals into
order into chaos into massive existence
into massive emptiness collapsing back
into death the soil sick with the lack
of death the holding of life the holding
of meta preventing the cycle from
happening enriching the soil with the
death that can give birth to new life
affording of matter locking defying of
death breaking it up piling a pyramid on
top of it so it cannot see and we cannot
see it looking at the eye of death
fearlessly seeing that does not despise
us if there's no hater nor does it smile
at us mothers that we love us it is it
just is
death is greedy for itself death is
gentle for all of life clean slates
fresh start
soil of potential sewage of the
aftermath mystical pillow-soft
all-consuming supportive regenerative
trusting pulling softening solidifying
transmutation all for love purification
[Music]
or complete breath purification a well
washed vessel fumigation intoxication
poison in the circulation purification
spinning around orbit of death all the
king purification through Putra fication
the gentle ugliness merciful disgust
discussing lifetimes cycles and evidence
lost to blackness of the winds of time
all the way down down down down down
down to the currents of heat its
conflict with the depths of cold pulling
light towards its inevitable and only to
blast it out again death like a shotgun
wound to the head
get like a cold knife stab to the side
death like a slow rising water filling
the lungs death like a plane that
consumes in an instant left like 45
years of illness the death of potential
rotting of the Apple discussed with the
seeds
[Music]
deaf like a cherry on top a life of
fulfillment sweetness the final curtain
dropping on our heads so the last thing
we see is the audience and we become the
seeds of the apple driven deep down into
the ground until the light pulls us up
again in an environment strong enough to
hold our roots until death becomes the
final cherry on top yet again
[Music]